<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc.</string>
    <string name="Login">Submit</string>
    <string name="Clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="LoginID">LoginID</string>
    <string name="Password">Password</string>
    <string name="Description">Description Holder</string>
    <string name="Name">Name Holder</string>
    <string name="MemberStatus">Member Status</string>
    <string name="SpouseName">Spouse Name</string>
    <string name="Address">Address</string>
    <string name="PrimaryContact">Primary Contact</string>
    <string name="SecondaryContact">Secondary Contact</string>
    <string name="Email">Email</string>
    <string name="Text">Text</string>
    <string name="Call">Call</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search the directory</string>

    <string name="PlaceHolder">Place Holder</string>
    <string name="member_status">Member Status</string>
    <string name="more_info">More Info</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="bio_info">Biographical Info</string>
    <string name="year_active">Year Turned Active</string>
    <string name="dyk">Did You Know?</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="userNoBio">You don\'t have a bio yet. Tap here to add one</string>
    <string name="error_save">Error: Information was not successfully saved</string>
    <string name="succ_save">Information successfully saved</string>
    <string name="cfgc_member_since">CFGC Member Since</string>
    <string name="azalea">2020 Azalea Garden Tour</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_text_from_azalea_tour_website_with_current_year_theme">
        \t\t\tCome enjoy Southern hospitality amid the vibrant color of azaleas and spring flowers
        during the 67th Annual Cape Fear Garden Club Azalea Garden Tour© in the beautiful
        coastal community of Wilmington, North Carolina. An official event of the North Carolina
        Azalea Festival, the tour is one of the longest running and most popular garden tours in
        the South. \n\t\t\tProceeds from the Cape Fear Garden Club Azalea Garden Tour© are
        reinvested in the community through beautification and horticultural grants within New
        Hanover County, scholarships at the University of North Carolina Wilmington and Cape
        Fear Community College, and conservation efforts at Battery Island, a National Audubon
        Society bird sanctuary. The club has granted over $1 million in donations to the community
        in the past 61 years.
    </string>
    <string name="_2020_gardens_and_map">2020 Gardens and Map</string>
    <string name="azalea_belles">Azalea Belles©</string>
    <string name="battery_island_committee">Battery Island Committee</string>
    <string name="civic_impact">Civic Impact</string>
    <string name="membership">Membership</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_text_from_battery_island_committee_info">
        \t\t\tBattery Island (established Fall 1996) – Battery Island Committee highlights the
        twenty-three-year relationship that The Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc. has in
        working closely with Audubon NC’s Coastal Office and biologists to maintain safe
        habitats for the migratory birds, specifically the islands in the Lower Cape Fear
        River where they nest. The Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc. assists Audubon in
        funding through a standing annual grant and through education outreach by
        sponsoring the annual Spring Cruise to the Bird Islands in the Lower Cape Fear
        River each May. \n\t\t\tThis committee supports Audubon with cleanups on Battery
        Island in the spring before nesting season begins and the fall after the nesting
        season is complete. Our main concern is to get debris that floats in off the Cape
        Fear River and specifically fishing line off the island because of the danger of
        entanglement of pelicans and other shorebirds. The Committee also does the
        detailed planning and coordination for The Cape Fear Garden Club for the
        Spring Cruise to the Bird Islands in the Lower Cape Fear River.
        \n\nthis needs to be fixed when I find it.</string>
    <string name="back_to_bird_islands_cruise">Back to Bird Islands Cruise</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_text_from_battery_island_cruise_and_ticket_info">
        Mark Your Calendar for the 2019 Cruise
        \n\t\t\tTickets are $40 and will be available beginning March 1 at Wild Bird and Garden
        located in Wilmington at Hanover Center and also in Southport.

        \n\nThe cruise is an educational experience and viewing is narrated by three experts
        who will share their knowledge with us:
        \n\t\t\t· Dr. James Parnell, Professor Emeritus of UNCW and North Carolina’s top ornithologist.
        \n\t\t\t· Walker Golder, National Audubon Society’s Director of the Eastern Flyway
        Coast Initiative which includes the North Carolina program as well as programs in
        eight states along the Atlantic Coast.
        \n\t\t\t· Lindsay Addison, Audubon North Carolina’s Coastal Biologist speaks
        describing her work to monitor the nesting colonies on the six bird islands the Cape
        Fear River including Battery Island.

        \n\n\t\t\tThe cruise will include islands in the lower Cape Fear River where the birds
        have chosen their nesting sites. They are all North Carolina Audubon Bird Sanctuaries.
        \n\t\t\tBring your camera and binoculars to view nesting areas of many coastal water
        birds including pelicans, white ibis, great egrets and herons. Pack a picnic lunch
        if you would like. Soft drinks, water and snacks will be sold aboard ship.

        \n\nAdditional information is available by emailing birdislandscruise@capefeargardenclub.org
        \nWhen and Where:

        \n\nSunday, May 19, 2019
        \nBoarding: 12:30 pm
        \nDeparting: 1:00 pm
        \nReturn: Approx 5:30 pm

        \n\nDeparting from Carolina Beach Marina on the Royal Winner Princess II

        \n\nAddress: 100 Carl Winner Ave, Carolina Beach, NC
    </string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_information_from_the_club_theme_page_on_website">This box is going to contain information from the Club theme page on website.</string>
    <string name="community_projects">Community Projects</string>
    <string name="lasting_legacy">Lasting Legacy</string>
    <string name="grants">Grants</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_information_from_the_community_projects_page_on_website">
        \t\t\tFor over 50 years, the Azalea Garden Tour, sponsored by Cape Fear Garden Club, has proudly
        returned thousands of dollars to New Hanover County. Tour profits Money available to beautify,
        conserve, educate, inspire, and contribute to people of all ages using horticulture and garden
        development.
    </string>
    <string name="back_to_civic_impact">Back to Civic Impact</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_information_from_the_grant_app_page_benefits_of_grants_and_recent_grants_awarded">
        \t\t\tGrant Recipients on 2018 were awarded $72,326 on November 14, 2018. The Cape Fear Garden
        Club is pleased to have David Johnson, owner of Johnson Nursery-Gardens Direct, as a sponsor for
        the 2018 Grant Recipients. Each of the twenty-six recipients received a $300 credit to be used at his
        nursery located in Willard or by ordering on line.

        \n\nAirlie Gardens Butterfly House
        \nAlliance for Cape Fear Trees
        \nBellamy Mansion Museum
        \nBrigade Boys and Girls Club
        \nCameron Art Museum
        \nCape Fear Clinic, Inc
        \nCape Fear Habitat for Humanity
        \nChildren’s Museum of Wilmington
        \nCoastal Preparatory Academy
        \nCodington Elementary School
        \nCommunity Enrichment Initiative, Inc
        \nDREAMS of Wilmington, Inc
        \nFirst Christian Church
        \nFriends of New Hanover County Arboretum
        \nFriends of Oakdale Cemetery
        \nThe Greater Wilmington Youth Initiative, Inc
        \nLake Forest Academy
        \nLower Cape Fear Historical Society
        \nLower Cape Fear Hospice
        \nNew Hanover County Arboretum Ability
        \nNew Hanover Parks and Gardens – Veterans Park
        \nNew Hanover High School
        \nNorth Carolina Coastal Federation
        \nSt. Andrews-Covenant Presbyterian Church
        \nWrightsville Beach Museum of History
        \nYMCA of Southeastern North Carolina
        \nStanding Grants
        \nNorth Carolina Audubon Society Grant
        \nCape Fear Community College Scholarship
        \nUniversity of North Carolina Wilmington Scholarship
    </string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_information_from_the_endowment_history_page_on_website">
        \t\t\tFor almost 90 years the Cape Fear Garden Club has worked to enhance and support
        the natural beauty of Wilmington. In 2011, we created the Cape Fear Garden Club
        Beautification Endowment to create perpetual funding to promote wide scale enhancement
        and maintenance of the landscapes of our city gateways, medians, byways and public
        spaces. Below is an overview of how recent grants benefit our Wilmington community:

        \n\nBEAUTIFICATION:

        \n\nThe creation of new gardens and the restoration of existing gardens;
        adding trees, shrubs; flowers along with hardscapes that will allow people to enjoy the particular area.

        \n\n\t\t\tChildren’s Museum – Secret Garden off Orange Street in which area residents,
        visitors and tourists can rest and relax
        \n\t\t\tCarolina Beach – enhancement of the “Town Gazebo”, central to this community
        \n\t\t\tSchools: Wilmington Christian, NHHS, Hoggard, Forest Hills Elementary, CFCC,
        Roland Grise Middle, Isaac Bear, Friends School, Gregory Elementary, Lake Forest Academy,
        St Mary’s, Wrightsville Beach Elementary, Noble Middle and Holly Tree Elementary
        \n\t\t\tJuvenile Day Treatment Center – gateway to Wilmington along side of this building
        \n\t\t\tKure Beach – enhancement of areas surrounding city signs
        \n\t\t\tLower Cape Fear Historical Society – Latimer House
        \n\t\t\tCity of Wilmington – Greenfield Amphitheater
        \n\t\t\tAirlie Gardens – Improve center drive of the gardens with irrigation, plant materials and mulch (2013)
        \n\t\t\tCameron Art Museum – Creation of a quilt garden from the museum’s collection.
        It is a slave-made tulip quilt. Funding is for all plantings in this garden (2013)
        \n\t\t\tBellamy Mansion Museum – re-activate 1861 cistern and rainwater harvesting system
        \n\t\t\tRotary Clubs of Wilmington (for Greenfield Park) – completion of irrigation project and Rotary
        Wheel for Wilmington Parks and Recreation
        \n\t\t\tFriends of the Battleship North Carolina – Improve Battleship Park with plants, mulch and soil (2013)
        \n\t\t\tWilmington Tree Commission – 200 azaleas and 9 Live Oaks on Market Street between 4th and 16th Streets
        \n\t\t\tCape Fear Community College – Beautify the circular courtyard at the Hanover parking deck (2013)



        \n\n\n\nCONSERVATION:

        \n\nSupports the CFGC’s ongoing project at Battery Island which was just increased from $4000 to $6000
        awarded each year.  This is a partnership with the Audubon Society with Walker Goldman and includes
        a bi-annual cleanup with plantings of Yaupon shrubs which help provide nesting sites for coastal birds,
        in particular the White Ibis which has one of its largest nesting sites right here at Battery Island.
        Other recent conservation grant projects have included:

        \n\n\t\t\tThe Arboretum new entrance which will feature storm water best management practice demonstration site (2008)
        \n\t\t\tCape Fear Community College Foundation – horticultural fitness trail which includes preservation of native carnivorous plants (2007)
        \n\t\t\tCape Fear River Watch – created an Urban Rain Garden to manage storm water runoff from headquarters building on Surry St;
        utilized native plants and conservation landscaping techniques to create an education site in front of the building (2007)
        \n\t\t\tLower Cape Fear Historical Society – Restore storm drains at sides of the 1852 Latimer House and improve irrigation (2013)
        \n\t\t\tNorth Carolina Coastal Federation – Native plants and shrubs for rain gardens at Bradley Creek and Alderman Elementary Schools (2013)
        \n\t\t\tNorth Carolina Land Trust – Supplies for propagation of new plants to restore Venus Flytraps at the Stanley Rehder Carivorous Garden(2013)



        \n\n\n\nEDUCATIONAL:

        \n\nMultiple grant awards have gone to schools and organizations for the purpose of educating
        people about how to use plants for conservation, food, landscaping, attracting wildlife, etc.

        \n\n\t\t\tAirlie Butterfly Garden – CFGC supplied the funds to landscape the entire area surrounding the new Butterfly Garden at Airlie Gardens .
        \n\t\t\tCape Fear Community College – funds for a greenhouse in which students learn to grow plants (now named the
        “Cape Fear Garden Club Greenhouse” in our club’s honor for our support). CFCC is also a partner in landscaping Habitat
        for Humanity homes as a part of their landscaping curriculum
        \n\t\t\tArboretum – Plant additional 45 camellia plants and companion plants in the former specimen and patio garden
        \n\t\t\tThe Davis Community – Create an outdoor destination to draw people from their rooms to experience nature (2013)
        \n\t\t\tCreekwood Community – an ongoing project to raise vegetables, engage community participation, educate and improve the health of area residents

        \n\nSCHOOLS:

        \n\n\t\t\tWilmington Academy of Arts and Sciences – vegetable gardens and a Snow Pea “Tee-Pee” to teach students
        a scientific introduction to vegetable gardening including the process of preparing beds, planting, composting,
        harvesting, and eating the crop produced
        \n\t\t\tCommunities in Schools – this center for at-risk youth will design, implement and maintain a flower and vegetable
        garden and hopefully sell the products at the Farmer’s Market downtown
        \n\t\t\tYahweh Center – working garden of flowers, herbs and vegetables including a greenhouse for hands on learning for children
        \n\t\t\tJT Hoggard – shade garden and education for Horticultural students in implementation and maintenance
        \n\t\t\tBellamy Elementary Garden Club – flower beds to be used in education and to improve self esteem
        \n\t\t\tNHHS – English as a second Language Students will install and maintain senior courtyard plantings
        \n\t\t\tLaney Highschool – Senior class garden, provide mulch and plantings (2013)

        \n\nINSPIRATION AND MEMORIALS:

        \n\n\t\t\tLower Cape Fear Hospice received monies to help with a 3 phase project for gardens on the property that will be
        uplifting to patients as well as to the entire community who visit and contemplate life and death. In 2013 Hospice was awarded
        a grant to cover all the plantings for new courtyards created as part of the campaign to expand the Pavilion
        \n\t\t\tUNCW students applied for and received a grant to beautify an area on campus and create a memorial garden
        for students and faculty who have died
        \n\t\t\tAshley High School TrrM Society – memorial garden
        \n\t\t\tLittle Chapel on the Boardwalk – Biblical Garden established on their property off “The Loop” – also educational
        as to plant materials found in the Old Testament
        \n\t\t\tWilmington Firefighters’ Memorial – Purchase materials for the irrigation system, a load of topsoil and perennials
        for the garden (2013)

        \n\nPHILANTHROPIC:

        \n\n\t\t\tHabitat for Humanity – for 4 years, we have funded plant materials to landscape homes for this organization;
        CFCC students provide the labor.  Habitat residents undergo a 12 week program to teach them how to own their
        own home and maintain it.

        \n\nENDOWED SCHOLARSHIPS:

        \n\n\t\t\tCape Fear Community College
        \n\t\t\tUniversity of North Carolina, Wilmington
    </string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_text_from_history_page_and_purpose_pages_from_website">
        CAPE FEAR GARDEN CLUB, INC
        \nWILMINGTON, NORTH CAROLINA

        \n\nORGANIZED FEBRUARY 11, 1925
        \nFederated with The Garden Club of North Carolina, Inc., 1929
        \nFederated with The National Garden Clubs, Inc., 1930
        \nMember of the South Atlantic Region, 1933
        \nMember of District 11
        \nAffiliated Member North Carolina Wildlife Federation, 1999

        \n\nMOTTO
        \n“And the Lord God planted a Garden…and there He put Man”….Genesis 2:8
        \nAdopted September 9, 1953

        \n\nCOLORS
        \nGreen and Yellow

        \n\nFLOWER
        \nCarolina Yellow Jessamine (Gelsemium sempervirens)

        \n\nCAPE FEAR GARDEN CLUB SEAL
        \nAdopted March 25, 1997, designed by Myrta W. Spence, CFGC

        \n\nEstablished North Carolina State Butterfly (SB236) Eastern Tiger Swallowtail
        \nJune 18, 2012

        \n\nTHE OBJECTIVES SHALL BE….

        \n\n\t\t\tTo provide a non-profit, philanthropic, and educational association for the members.
        \n\t\t\tTo stimulate knowledge and the love of gardening.
        \n\t\t\tTo study, in all its aspects, the art of gardening, particularly horticulture, and to cooperate
        with other agencies furthering such interest.
        \n\t\t\tTo encourage environmental improvement through civic development, beautification,
        restoration, and to aid in the protection and conservation of our native trees, plants, and birds.
        \n\t\t\tCape Fear Garden Club, Inc. is a registered, non-profit corporation which is exempt from
        US Federal income tax under Section 501© 3 of the Internal Revenue Code.

        \n\nCharter Members 1925

        \n\nMrs. N.M. Martin, President
        \nMrs. W.A. Graham, Recording Secretary
        \nMrs. John Bolles
        \nMrs. A.M. Hall
        \nMrs. Hugh MacRae
        \nMrs. Platt W. Davis
        \nMrs. R.H. Hubbard
        \nMiss Jeanie Strange
        \nMrs. W.E. Elliott
        \nMrs. William Latimer
        \nMrs. Martin Willard
        \nMiss Sarah Lippitt
    </string>
    <string name="members_only">Members Only</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_the_contact_us_info_from_the_website">
        Our USPS Mailing Address:
        \nCape Fear Garden Club, Inc.
        \nP.O. Box 4751 Wilmington, NC 28406
        \nFor General Inquires:
        \ninfo[@]CapeFearGardenClub.org

        \n\nPresident of the Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc.:
        \nRebecca Philpott
        \nPresident[@]CapeFearGardenClub.org

        \n\nFor information about the Bird Islands Cruise:
        \nMarlene Eader
        \nbirdislandscruise[@]capefeargardenclub.org

        \n\nMedia Questions and Interview Requests:
        \nBarbara Downing
        \npublicity[@]capefeargardenclub.org

        \n\nAzalea Garden Tour Media Questions and Interview Requests:
        \nNina Brown or Barbara Downing
        \ngardentourpublicity[@]capefeargardenclub.org

        \n\nCape Fear Garden Club, Inc. Azalea Belles:
        \nKaren Smith
        \nAzaleaBellesChair[@]CapeFearGardenClub.org

        \n\nWebmaster:
        \nRahel Haley
        \nWebmaster[@]CapeFearGardenClub.org
</string>
    <string name="back_to_membership">Back to Membership</string>
    <string name="username_or_email">Username or Email</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_the_membership_directory">Welcome to the Membership Directory</string>
    <string name="username_contactemail">Username [ContactEmail]</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="back_to_events">Back to Events</string>
    <string name="sort_by_first_name_or_last_name">Sort by First Name or Last Name</string>
    <string name="the_cape_fear_garden_club_inc">The Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc.</string>
    <string name="last">Last</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="sort_first">Sort First</string>
    <string name="sort_last">Sort Last</string>
    <string name="_2020_azalea_gardens_map">2020 Azalea Gardens Map</string>
    <string name="this_box_will_contain_info_about_the_azalea_belles">This box will contain info about the Azalea Belles.</string>
    <string name="no_name">No name is set, tap here to set one.</string>
    <string name="no_spouse_name">No spouse name is set, tap here to set one.</string>
    <string name="no_address">No address is set, tap here to set one.</string>
    <string name="no_primary">No primary contact is set, tap here to set one.</string>
    <string name="no_secondary">No secondary contact is set, tap here to set one.</string>
    <string name="edit_address">Edit Address</string>
    <string name="street_address">Street Address</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="state">State</string>
    <string name="zip_code">Zip Code</string>
    <string name="asd">asd</string>
    <string name="edit_name">Edit Name</string>
    <string name="this_box_is_going_to_contain_text_from_azalea_belles_website_photos_policies_and_belle_application_info">
        Azalea Belle Policies and Application Information
        \n2019 Azalea Belle Application Information

        \n\nApplications for the 2019 Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc. Azalea Belles © will be available to high school
        juniors and seniors on January 23, 2019 from members of the Cape Fear Garden Club (CFGC) or the Azalea
        Belle Committee. Young ladies desiring to become a Belle should contact a member of the CFGC to ask
        if they will sponsor you and help you complete an application. Juniors must have a CFGC member sponsor.
        For Seniors ONLY: If you do not know a CFGC member, you may go to 1309 Honor Lane at 4:00 PM on
        January 23rd. to be interviewed by the Belle Committee and receive an application from them. Please refer
        to the Azalea Belle policy as posted on this website. Belle Applications for 2019 closed at midnight on January 30th.
        \nAZALEA BELLE POLICIES (adopted 2006; revised 2018)

        \n\nCFGC Belle Mission Statement: The Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc. Azalea Belles © serve as ambassadors
        for The Cape Fear Garden Club Inc., the North Carolina Azalea Festival and the City of Wilmington.
        This is a diverse group of young women dressed in colorful gowns that complement the blooms and surrounding
        landscapes of Wilmington, greet visitors to the Cape Fear Garden Club Azalea Garden Tour©, and participate
        in other events related to the North Carolina Azalea Festival.

        \n\n1. The Azalea Belle Committee is composed of members of The Cape Fear Garden Club, Inc.

        \n\n2. The purpose of the Azalea Belle Committee is to assist the Belle Chairmen with the initial contacting of
        the Belle, the dress fittings, the tea, the rehearsal, the ribbon cutting, and any other activities in which assistance is needed.

        \n\n3. The Belle applications will be distributed each year at the January meeting of the Cape Fear Garden
        Club to members of the Cape Fear Garden Club.

        \n\n4. Cape Fear Garden Club members may sponsor no more than 3 young ladies who meet the criteria*
        specified on the Belle information sheet attached to the application. Sponsors are responsible for informing
        the Belle and her parents of her responsibilities to the Garden Club.

        \n\n5. Senior girls who wish to be Belles and do not have a garden club sponsor may apply through the
        Belle Chairmen. Her sponsor will be listed as “committee sponsored.” This policy allows more girls to
        have this opportunity and it helps us to be more diverse. ALL JUNIOR APPLICANTS MUST have a
        garden club sponsor for their application to be accepted – NO EXCEPTIONS (any junior who wishes
        to apply but cannot find a garden club sponsor may reapply through the Belle Committee or through
        a garden club sponsor her senior year).

        \n\n6. The Belle Chairmen will determine the number of Belles needed for each garden tour based on
        the sizes of the gardens. The number may vary from year to year. In other words, there is no set number.

        \n\n7. Belle applications must be mailed to the address listed on the application and they must be
        postmarked by the date listed on the application. Applications received after the set postmark date
        will not be considered. NO EXCEPTIONS!

        \n\n8. Belle selection will be conducted by the Belle committee chairs using the following guidelines:

        \n\n\t\t\ta. Daughters and granddaughters of CFGC members will be given first priority regardless of where the
        girl resides. High school seniors who attend school or reside in New Hanover County. High school juniors who
        attend school or reside in New Hanover County. If there are more junior applications than slots available after
        placing the above, a random lottery will be conducted from the junior applicants by the Belle Chairmen. (We
        are no longer accepting any sophomore applications due to the numbers of juniors and seniors applying each year.)

        \n\n\t\t\tb. Young ladies of appropriate age from surrounding counties may apply, but their applications
        will not be given priority over any of the above.

        \n\n9. The Belle Chairmen will mail acceptance letters to the young ladies who are selected.
        Letters of regret will be mailed to those not selected. If a young lady is not selected, she will have to go
        through the application process again the following year if she is eligible and wishes to be considered.
        We do not keep a waiting list.

        \n\n10. The Belle Chairmen will select the Belles who will participate in the special activities.
        (Examples: trip to Raleigh, photo shoots for publicity, parade floats, the Queen’s arrival, etc.)
        When possible, daughters and granddaughters will be considered for these activities. It is not
        always possible or fair to always place only daughters and granddaughters in all the special activities.

        \n\n11. The dressmakers for the Belles are secured by the chairmen annually. The chairmen
        and the dressmakers will determine the dates for the fittings. Committee members will assist
        with the fittings. If a Belle has her own gown or would like to have her own gown made by someone
        other than the designated dressmakers, she will have to have the pattern and fabric approved by the Belle Chairmen.

        \n\n12. These policies will remain in effect until the committee decides changes need to be made.

        \n\n*Criteria:

        \n\n\t\t\tApplications are accepted from young ladies who are in the 11th or 12th grade and who reside in or attend school
        in New Hanover County. Applications from surrounding counties are accepted, but are not given priority over New Hanover
        County applicants. (Daughters and granddaughters of CFGC members may reside out of town.)
        \n\t\t\tA young lady may only serve as a Belle one year.
        \n\t\t\tA young lady who wishes to be a Belle may not participate in the Azalea Festival Scholarship Pageant
        in the same year she serves as a Belle.

        \n\n*************************
        \nQuestions regarding this policy should be directed to Karen Smith, Chairperson of the Azalea Belle
        Committee: karen.smith1309@gmail.com or 910-620-6958.
    </string>
</resources>
